Someone is out there
running around
and disabling my puppets.
Can you go and kill them?
Yes, you can count on me.
I'll take all of 'em down.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
TRACKING X AND X PURSUIT
[Knuckle] He's close.
[Shoot] Very well.
He's still on the road.
If he stays the course,
he'll pass by here
in ten minutes.
[Shoot] Do you really think
he'll stick to the road?
[Knuckle] No.
He'll notice my presence
just before he gets here,
announces accumulated interest
every ten seconds,
and A.P.R. informs the enemy
interest will be accrued,
but the count is interrupted
if the target gets more than
100 meters away from Knuckle.
The remaining time
is then stored,
saved in A.P.R.'s memory,
and then as soon as the target
gets within a 100-meter radius
of Knuckle once again,
the count picks up
exactly where it left off.
[Knuckle] He's approaching at
a speed between 160 to 180 kph.
If there are still
three seconds or more
before A.P.R.
adds interest again,
[Shoot] What's wrong?
[Knuckle] Damn it.
What just happened?
He changed direction
at the last second!
-[Shoot] Huh?
-[Knuckle] There!
-[Shoot] Calm down.
-[growls]
It's not worth it.
He has the speed of a cheetah.
We'll never catch up.
[Knuckle] He's not supposed
to know how to deal with Zetsu.
How the hell did he
discover our ambush?
Wait.
There's no point in doing more work
than absolutely necessary.
[Flutter] Right.
It appears
that they were attempting
to ambush sir Cheetu.
[Leol] Oh. So he's in the area?
[Flutter] I warned sir Cheetu
before he ran into their trap.
Was that unnecessary?
[Leol] What did he do?
[Flutter] He took a detour
toward the capital.
He told me that I should
thank you for the help.
[Leol] I see. Good work.
He owes me one now.
[cellphone rings]
Leol here.
[Neferpitou] The target
just engaged a squad of soldiers
in the city of Luonton.
[Leol] Luonton?
Start preparing an ambush
to the north of them.
They've had to stay
in one particular area
for longer than expected, meow.
We should all bear in mind
that they have been
constantly on the move
for more than 30 hours straight.
[tense music playing]
-[man 1] Liar!
-[man 2] Rebel scum!
as many puppets
and soldiers as I can.
Well, should I try heading north?
[Gon] I knew it.
Someone's still following me.
Who's there?
Come out, and show yourself!
[footsteps stop]
[Gon] The presence is gone.
It might just be following me
until more ants show up.
-[Leol] Hey.
-Hey.
[Leol] Sorry that I
had to stop you.
[Cheetu] Nah. I was
already headed this way.
Is the king this direction, Hagya?
[growls]
[Cheetu] Flutter's warning
was a really big help to me.
I'm trying to avoid
getting into fights right now.
[Leol] Glad to hear it.
By the way, what's that thing?
It just follows me
wherever I run to.
I guess I'm stuck with it,
I said, you want it gone?
You can do that?
Probably.
But it'll cost me?
[Leol] The royal guard
has assigned me a mission.
I'd like your help on it.
-[Flutter] Sir Leol.
-[Leol] Hmm?
[Flutter] I've spotted the target.
He's headed north on the road
through the forest
northeast of Luonton.
It seems
that Lord Neferpitou's hunch
was right on the money.
You said he's a Hunter?
They can be pretty difficult
to deal with.
I know. I've planned ahead.
Okay.
With any luck,
you can master it in a day.
I'm a slow learner,
[Cheetu] When you
put it like that, sure.
I'll have my underlings
determine the prey's abilities.
Yeah, I guess I owe you one.
[Cheetu] Sounds like you're
looking to reclaim your throne.
[Killua] Damn it.
I'm being followed.
And he's way out of yo-yo range.
If I don't lose him or beat him,
I'm in trouble.
[Killua] The canopy leaves
are dense enough
that he shouldn't be able
to see me from the air,
and if he comes down here,
he'll be in range of my yo-yo.
[Killua panting]
[Killua] Something's coming
from the opposite side,
and it's on the ground.
[gasps]
Huh?
[Beetle Ant] Huh?
-[Monkey Ant] Aha!
-[Chimera Ants yell]
[neck cracks]
-[Monkey Ant] No!
-[Killua yelps]
Retreat! Time to regroup!
[Beetle Ant laughing]
Well, what do you say, kid?
How'd you like that blast?
No, there's a bigger problem.
I completely concealed my presence
and attacked from his blind spot,
but he countered
at the perfect time.
Someone must be
feeding him information.
It's him.
He's probably
watching right now.
I'd guess he's got a power that
lets him pinpoint my location.
I don't want them to know about
my electro-shocks, or my yo-yo.
I'd like to shake them off
and go back to hiding,
but that won't work.
I'll have
to beat them all without…
No. There's something
stuck to my face.
[flea chatters]
[Killua] A flea?
[dramatic music playing]
[Flutter] Area TH-88,
X-15, Y-12, Z-2.
Point X-9, Y-3, Z-1.
[beeping]
♪ There's no escaping ♪
[flea chatters]
[Killua] Damn it!
My temple won't stop bleeding.
Point Y-5, X-3, Z-1.
Okay.
[inhales]
[Killua yelps]
[Sniper humming]
♪ My fleas are so special ♪
♪ So very, very special ♪
They have
a 200-meter vertical leap.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
[suspenseful music playing]
[Flutter] Ah.
He's going to try something.
He may try to use his ability.
[Sniper] Yeah.
[Flutter] Let's see
what he can do.
[Sniper] Okay.
[inhales]
Nothing you can do
can escape my sight.
So come on. Do something!
[dramatic music playing]
[narrator] Killua cannot use En.
Killua knows this and keeps his
aura within a manageable range,
just 57 centimeters
from his body.
is within that range,
Killua must rely
on his incredible reflexes
as well as his strength
to react with desperate speed
and dodge the enemy's attack
at point-blank range.
The margin of error
is unfortunately
all but nonexistent.
But this time,
he did not dodge it.
This way, he could determine
the bullet's trajectory.
[grunts]
Damn it.
It came from this way!
[dramatic music playing]
[Flutter] Ah.
He allowed himself to be hit
so he could locate the sniper.
The target is heading your way,
and quickly!
[Sniper] Okay.
♪ This is all
Within expected parameters ♪
[Killua] The bleeding's
completely stopped
You like that?
Now there's
nowhere for you to hide,
so come on out!
[Meleoron] Wait!
The desert is massive.
If you don't have any water,
you'll die of thirst in a day.
-[footsteps]
-[gasps]
[Meleoron] Aw, man.
I wanted to observe you
a little longer,
but I guess that won't work.
First, introductions.
Hello. My name is Jail…
Uh, I mean call me Meleoron.
I was a squadron leader
when the Queen was alive.
Nice to meet you.
And what's your name?
Why were you following me?
Because I didn't
want you getting away,
and I sure couldn't
just let you die,
[gasps]
I almost let it slip.
He approached me
with an ulterior motive.
-[Gon] "You guys"?
-[Meleoron gasps]
[laughs]
Yeah, that's right.
[Meleoron gasps]
[Gon] And you picked me
over Killua.
Thought I'd put up
less of a fight, didn't you?
[Meleoron] Huh? Wait!
You've got it all wrong!
Is that how it sounded?
Okay, that makes sense.
I mean, I know what I look like.
You think I'm an enemy.
Guess I should have been
more clear about that.
Listen, I swear I'm not lying!
I'm not looking to trick
or defeat you, okay? Promise.
[Killua] Is that him?
[dramatic music playing]
♪ It's a trap ♪
♪ Come on in if you wanna ♪
[Ikalgo]
He went for the kill
instantly and
without hesitation.
I'm impressed.
[gags]
[Killua] A lake?
It's Captain Ikalgo's host!
[Fish Ant 1]
Stop eating it, damn it!
[Fish Ant 2] Look,
I want to stop, but I can't!
[Fish Ant 1]
The blood is calling us!
[closing theme music playing]
[narrator] Killua's opponent is Ikalgo,
a Chimera Ant
resembling an octopus
that uses human hosts.
[Ikalgo]
Don't call me an octopus!
[singer singing in Japanese]
[dramatic music playing]
[Gon] Next time,
"Ikalgo and Lightning."